<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<component type="desktop">
  <id>org.kde.cervisia.desktop</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-2.0+</project_license>
  <name>Cervisia</name>
  <name xml:lang="ast">Cervisia</name>
  <name xml:lang="bs">Cervisia</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca">Cervisia</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca-valencia">Cervisia</name>
  <name xml:lang="cs">Cervisia</name>
  <name xml:lang="da">Cervisia</name>
  <name xml:lang="de">Cervisia</name>
  <name xml:lang="en-GB">Cervisia</name>
  <name xml:lang="es">Cervisia</name>
  <name xml:lang="et">Cervisia</name>
  <name xml:lang="fr">Cervisia</name>
  <name xml:lang="gl">Cervisia</name>
  <name xml:lang="it">Cervisia</name>
  <name xml:lang="ko">Cervisia</name>
  <name xml:lang="nl">Cervisia</name>
  <name xml:lang="pl">Cervisia</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt">Cervisia</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt-BR">Cervisia</name>
  <name xml:lang="sk">Cervisia</name>
  <name xml:lang="sl">Cervisia</name>
  <name xml:lang="sv">Cervisia</name>
  <name xml:lang="tr">Cervisia</name>
  <name xml:lang="uk">Cervisia</name>
  <name xml:lang="x-test">xxCervisiaxx</name>
  <name xml:lang="zh-CN">Cervisia</name>
  <name xml:lang="zh-TW">版本控制_Cervisia</name>
  <description>
    <p>
      Cervisia is a user friendly version control system front-end. The aim is to support CVS and other version control system
      programs in a unified interface, featuring conflict resolution, difference and history viewers, status for the working
      copy files, and support for most version control functions.
    </p>
    <p xml:lang="bs">Cervisia je korisniči orijentisani sistem za praćenje kontrole verzija. Cilj je da se podrži CVS i druge programi za kontrolu verzija u jedinstven interfejs, koji obuhvata rješavanje konflikta, preglednike razlika i istorije, status za radne kopije datoteka, i podršku za većinu funkcija kontrole verzija.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">El Cervisia és un frontal amigable del sistema pel control de versions. El seu objectiu és implementar el CVS i altres programes del sistema de control de versions en una interfície unificada, amb resolució de conflictes, diferències i visors de l'historial, estat dels fitxers de la còpia de treball, i admet la majoria de les funcions pel control de versions.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca-valencia">El Cervisia és un frontal amigable del sistema pel control de versions. El seu objectiu és implementar el CVS i altres programes del sistema de control de versions en una interfície unificada, amb resolució de conflictes, diferències i visors de l'historial, estat dels fitxers de la còpia de treball, i admet la majoria de les funcions pel control de versions.</p>
    <p xml:lang="de">Cervisia ist eine anwenderfreundliche Benutzeroberfläche für Versionsverwaltungssysteme. Die Zielsetzung besteht darin eine einheitliche Oberfläche für CVS und andere Versionsverwaltungen zu schaffen, die das Auflösen von Versionskonflikten, die Darstellung von Versionsunterschieden und Änderungsverläufen und die Verwaltung von lokalen Arbeitskopien anbietet.</p>
    <p xml:lang="en-GB">Cervisia is a user friendly version control system front-end. The aim is to support CVS and other version control system programs in a unified interface, featuring conflict resolution, difference and history viewers, status for the working copy files, and support for most version control functions.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">Cervisia es una amigable interfaz de sistema de control de versiones. Está pensada para implementar CVS y otros programas de sistema de control de versiones usando una interfaz unificada, proporcionando resolución de conflictos, visores de diferencias y de historial, estado de los archivos de la copia de trabajo e implementación de la mayor parte de las funciones de control de versiones.</p>
    <p xml:lang="et">Cervisia on kasutajasõbralik versioonihaldussüsteemi kasutajaliides. Selle eesmärk on toetada CVS-i ja muid versioonihaldussüsteemi programme ühtse liidesena, mis võimaldab lahendada konflikte, vaadata erinevusi ja ajalugu, näha töös olevate failide staatust ja üldse kasutada enamikku võimalusi, mida versioonihaldussüsteemid pakuvad.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">Cervisia est une interface utilisateur agréable pour les gestionnaires de révision. L'objectif est la prise en charge de CVS et d'autres systèmes de contrôle de révision au sein d'une interface unifiée fournissant la résolution des conflits, l'affichage des différences et des historiques, l'affichage de l'état de la copie de travail ainsi que la prise en charge de la plupart des fonctionnalités des systèmes de contrôle de révision.</p>
    <p xml:lang="gl">Cervisia é unha interface gráfica para o control de versións. O propósito é soportar CVS e outros programas de control de versións cunha interface unificada, fornecendo visores para a resolución de conflitos, diferenzas e historial, estado dos ficheiros da copia de traballo, e soporte para a maioría das funcións do control de versións.</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">Cervisia è un'interfaccia grafica per sistemi di gestione delle revisioni. Il suo obiettivo è la gestione uniforme di CVS ed altri sistemi per il controllo delle revisioni, con funzioni come la risoluzione di conflitti, visori per le differenze e la cronologia, stato dei file della copia di lavoro e gestione della maggior parte delle funzioni di controllo delle versioni.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ko">Cervisia는 버전 관리 시스템 프론트엔드입니다. CVS와 다른 버전 관리 시스템을 통합된 인터페이스로 지원하고, 충돌 해결, 차이 및 기록 보기, 작업 사본 상태 보기, 여러 버전 관리 시스템 기능을 지원합니다.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Cervisia is een front-end van een gebruikersvriendelijk versiecontrolsysteem. Het doel is de ondersteuning van CVS en andere programma's voor versiecontrolsystemen in een gemeenschappelijk interface, met oplossen van conflicten, verschillen en tonen van de historie, status van de bestanden van de werkkopie en ondersteuning voor de meeste functies van een versiecontrolsysteem.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">Cervisia jest przyjazną użytkownikowi nakładką graficzną na system sterowania wersją. Celem jest obsługa CVS i innych programów do sterowania wersją przy pomocy ujednoliconego układu sterowania wraz z rozwiązywaniem niezgodności, przeglądarką różnic i historii, stanem plików kopi roboczej oraz obsługą większości możliwości sterowania wersją.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">O Cervisia é uma interface amigável para os sistemas de controlo de versões. O objectivo é suportar o CVS e os outros sistemas de controlo de versões com uma interface unificada, oferecendo a resolução de conflitos, as visualizações das diferenças e do histórico, o estado para os ficheiros da cópia local e o suporte para a maioria das funções de controlo de versões.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt-BR">Cervisia é uma interface amigável ao usuário para o sistema de controle de versão. O objetivo é ter suporte ao CVS e outros programas de sistemas de controle de versão em uma interface unificada, com recursos de resolução de conflitos, visualizadores de diferenças e histórico, estado para as cópias de trabalho dos arquivos, e suporte para maioria das funções de controle.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sk">Cervisia je používateľsky priateľská verzia frontendu na správu verzií. Jej cieľ je podpora CVS a iných programov na správu verzií v unifikovanom rozhraní, riešenie konfliktov, prehliadače rozdielov a histórie, stav pre súbory pracovnej kópie a podpora pre väčšinu funkcií správy verzií.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sl">Cervisia je uporabniku prijazno začelje sistema za nadzor različic. Cilj programa je podpora CVS in drugim sistemom za nadzor različic v enotnem vmesniku, ki podpira reševanje sporov, prikazuje razlike, zgodovino in stanje datotek delovne kopije ter podpira večino funkcij sistema za nadzor različic.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Cervisia är ett användarvänligt gränssnitt för versionskontrollsystem. Målet är att stödja CVS och andra program för versionskontroll med ett gemensamt gränssnitt, med funktioner för konfliktupplösning, jämförelse- och historikvisning, status för kopierade arbetsfiler, och stöd för de flesta versionskontrollfunktioner.</p>
    <p xml:lang="tr">Cervisia kullanıcı dostu bir sürüm kontrol sistemi ara yüzüdür. Hedefi CVS ve diğer sürüm kontrol sistemlerini birleştirilmiş bir arayüzde çakışmalara çözümler sunmak, fark ve geçmiş görünümleri ve çalışılan kopya dosyanın durumunu göstermek ve sürüm kontrol işlevlerinin çoğunu karşılamaktır.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Cervisia — зручна у користуванні оболонка до системи керування версіями. Метою її створення була підтримка CVS та інших систем керування версіями за допомогою універсального інтерфейсу, з можливостями розв’язання конфліктів, інструментами перегляду відмінностей і історії, стану файлів робочої копії та підтримкою більшості функціональних можливостей системи керування версіями.</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxCervisia is a user friendly version control system front-end. The aim is to support CVS and other version control system programs in a unified interface, featuring conflict resolution, difference and history viewers, status for the working copy files, and support for most version control functions.xx</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh-TW">Cervisia 是一套版本控制系統的前端介面。它可以用同一套介面支援 CVS 與其它版本控制系統，功能包括衝突解決，變更與歷史檢視，工作複本的狀態檢視，並支援許多其他的版本控制功能。</p>
  </description>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://bugs.kde.org/enter_bug.cgi?format=guided&amp;product=cervisia</url>
  <url type="help">http://docs.kde.org/stable/en/kdesdk/cervisia/index.html</url>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>http://kde.org/images/screenshots/cervisia.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <project_group>KDE</project_group>
  <provides>
    <binary>cervisia</binary>
  </provides>
</component>
